https://pagemasterpublishing.ca/privacy-policy/

Fine Art
More...
Fine Art
More...
0 items
$0.00
No products in the cart.
Fine Art
More...
Introduction
Canada’s national privacy legislation, the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act came into force on January 1, 2001. Since January 1, 2004, this privacy legislation applies to all businesses that collect, use or disclose Personal Information. Personal Information means information about you that can be used to identify you. Depending on the country or province you live in, you may have rights under similar laws.
We know that doing business online involves a great deal of trust on your part; we take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personally identifiable information you provide us. We pledge to protect your privacy and safeguard your personal information.
How we gather information from users
PageMaster Publication Services is the sole owner of the information collected on PageMasterPublishing.ca. PageMasterPublishing.ca collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
Registration
To use all features of this Web site (such as convenient orders and repeat downloads) you may choose to register. On registration you complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.
We’ll send you a confirmation email when your email address is signed up to ensure someone hasn’t done it on your behalf. Once you confirm your address, a welcome email will sent.
You will automatically be subscribed to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section. Unsubscribing from the newsletter does not close your account at PageMasterPublishing.ca. You can still use our services without receiving our newsletter.
Orders
When you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address).
We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
Your financial information is safe. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to accept credit cards and electronic check payments safely and securely for our customers. The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the electronic check and credit card processing networks. The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including: 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information.
PageMasterPublishing.ca is regularly tested to ensure compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS).
Surveys or Contests
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on PageMasterPublishing.ca.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code).
We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes and may use it to send participants an email newsletter.
We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.
Tell-A-Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  PageMasterPublishing.ca stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.
Your friend may contact us at orders_at_pagemaster.ca to request that we remove this information from our database.
What we do with the information we collect
PageMaster may collect personal information when you register, when you use our services and when you visit PageMasterPublishing.ca pages or the pages related to the content contained within PageMasterPublishing.ca. PageMaster may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies in order to provide services you have requested from PageMasterPublishing.ca. We do not purchase any personal data from other companies.
PageMasterPublishing.ca collects information about your transactions with us and your use of the services that we offer.
PageMasterPublishing.ca automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser settings, and pages requested.
PageMasterPublishing.ca also places a cookie, used only to keep track of your login status.
PageMasterPublishing.ca uses information for the following general purposes:
To fulfill your requests for products and services;
To improve our services;
To contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients;
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”
Newsletters
We will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.
Service-related Announcements
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.
Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.
Customer Service
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.
Profile
We store information that we collect through cookies and log files, to create a “profile” of your preferences.  We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.
We do not share your profile with other third parties.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Personally identifiable information:
PageMasterPublishing.ca does not share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies. We only share your personal information with third parties in the following circumstances:
Agents
We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
Service Providers
We use other third parties to provide shipping. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.
Other Third Parties
We may share information about you if PageMaster Publication Services Inc. is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, PageMaster will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy pledge.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise required by law;
We may disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PageMaster’s terms of use;
Information Transfers
PageMasterPublishing.ca will transfer personal information about you to other countries where we do business. In particular, PageMasterPublishing.ca will transfer personal information from Canada to the EU and the United States for the purposes of providing the services and products PageMasterPublishing.ca offers. Although other countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country where you reside, PageMasterPublishing.ca will apply the terms of this Privacy Policy to all personal information that it collects.
Choice/Opt-out
In compliance with the CASL and CAN-SPAM Acts, all e-mail sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.
We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications under My Account – My Profile or you may contact us at to opt-out.
You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.
You can edit your account information at any time. You can remove your credit card information by clicking the “Remove credit card information” link in the Account section of the My Account tab.
Certain communications from PageMasterPublishing.ca such as critical service announcements and administrative messages, are considered part of our membership and you may not opt out of receiving them if you are part of a membership. You may opt out of receiving the newsletter, meet-up invitations, and other non-critical communications under Manage Account Preferences in the My Account tab. This section is also where you can change the email address, password, country, and currency associated with your account.
You may delete your PageMasterPublishing.ca account by clicking the “Cancel my account” link in the Personal Information section of the My Account tab.
You may also correct, update, delete, or deactivate personal information by contacting us, or at the mailing address listed below.
If you use the PageMasterPublishing.ca comments you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.
Log Files
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click data.
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. PageMasterPublishing.ca will set and access PageMasterPublishing.ca cookies on your computer. The information stored by our cookies is linked only to your email and password. We do not link other personally identifiable information you provide to cookies.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.PageMasterPublishing.ca uses session ID cookies to ensure that you are recognized when you move from page to page within our site. These cookies are deleted when you close your browser.
We use persistent cookies to identify your time zone, and/or country, as well as to allow you to use the forums. You can manually delete cookies at any time by following the directions given in your Internet browser’s Help file. If you reject cookies, you will be able to browse the site, but you will not be able to purchase or publish any content or participate in the forums.
Links to Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by PageMaster Publication Services Inc. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If you have any questions about security on our Web site, please use the contact form or the contact information below.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
Copyright 2018 - PageMaster Publication Services Inc.
See Artists and Authors
